adstract.com 2012-10-05

# Privacy Policy | AdStract | Global Video & Display Marketplace Powered by adk2

AdStract, AdStract.com and PLYmedia (“AdStract”) have a strong commitment to protect the privacy of its users. Our privacy policy aims to ensure the protection of privacy of our users and to provide them with control over the decision how their information is being used.

**Acceptance of Terms**

By using or visiting AdStract or the AdStract Service (collectively referred to as the the “Website” or the “Service”), you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Website or Service. The Privacy Policy should read together with the Terms of Use and Copyright Policy which together comprise of the full agreement between AdStract and the users.

**Change of Policy**

AdStract reserves the right to change or modify the Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the modified Policy on the Website. Your continued use of the Website indicates your acceptance of any revised Policy.

**Information Gathered**

AdStract collects personal information only about its registered users (for purposes of providing the Service and making necessary payments or payment collection) and collects non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) from its Publishers’ users and visitors to improve the performance of the Website and Service and to assure quality of the Service and enrichment of the offerings to Publishers, Advertisers and their users and Visitors. In the process of registration or use of the AdStract service, you may be required to provide personal information including, but not limited to, User Name, Password, First and Last Name, Email Address, Country and other identifying information (including payment information).  
AdStract may further collect information about the time, type and manner of use of the Website or Service. This information may include information regarding the IP Address, time of usages, viewed files, and other information regarding the use of the Website.

**Use of Collected Information**

  1. AdStract has a strong commitment not to sell or rent your personal information to others, except when technologically necessary, authorized by you or demanded by law enforcement following due process.
  2. AdStract may provide your contact information to its partners and business affiliates to enrich your experience at the Website.
  3. You may be able to register to receive updates and promotions or site surveys. The contact information you submit will not be used for these purposes unless you specifically opt in, if available.
  4. Personally identifying information about the users will not be used for any purpose which is unrelated to the use of the Website or Services.
  5. AdStract may use the collected information about your browser, operating system or other technical details of your usage or the usage of your users or viewers to improve your experience at the Website or Service. We may further use the collected non-identifying information about usage patterns, including information about time of usage and form of usage to improve the experience and to be able to improve our offering to the users.
  6. AdStract may also collects additional non-PII information through cookies (non-tracking) that may be installed and approved by Your Visitors and provide such information to third-parties. Your Visitors have either agreed to the placement of the cookie or have been provided an opt-out as applicable and required by law (see below).

**Data and Information security**

AdStract is committed to protect the security of its users’ data and information and will take necessary steps to assure data and information security. Access to personally identifying information will be protected and controlled by password and restricted permissions. However, by using the Website or Service, you agree that AdStract will not be liable for any third party action, misuse, abuse or infringement of data and information security.

**Children’s Privacy**

AdStract is committed to protect children’s privacy and to follow the laws, regulations and guidelines in regard to children privacy. AdStract is committed to follow the guidelines established by the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. In accordance, AdStract will never knowingly accept or solicit personally identifiable information from a user known to be under the age of thirteen (13). If you have concerns regarding children privacy please contact us at support@AdStract.com. We are committed to act immediately to answer your concern.

**Privacy Opt-Out**

We may send marketing communications to users. If AdStract provides marketing communication, it shall enable you to opt-out of receiving marketing information, by un-checking the “I would like to receive email updates” box (or equivalent option in the newsletter) on the registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can edit your profile to update your privacy permissions and opt-out from receiving any further marketing communication.  
You may further opt-out of providing information to AdStract through its collection of non-PII from cookies placed on your computer, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-out>. By clicking on this opt-out link, AdStract will no longer collect non-PII information from your website or users (domain adk2.com). You may opt back in, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-in>.

**Use of Metadata**

AdStract may use the metadata which is created in the process of creating, editing, sharing or linking between AdStract’s content and Ad Units to enrich its customer’s experience and provide its customers and affiliates with useful information, in accord with its Privacy Policy. The metadata is AdStract’s property and/or the property of the copyright owner and AdStract reserves the right to share the metadata with its partners and affiliates. You are informed not to insert personally identifying information in the metadata unless you agree that such information will be shared.

**Disclosure of Information**

AdStract reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

**Disclaimer Regarding Linked Sites**

While using AdStract you may be linked from or to third parties sites. AdStract shall not be responsible for information, content, terms, offers or any other use of privacy policy at these sites. AdStract takes careful notice in choosing its business partners and affiliates and aims to partner only with reliable partners which our committed to users privacy. However, remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. By your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on the Website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Last Update: January 2012**
